Recording.
Yeah, maybe Jyotish,
we can go through the prototype and then
we will try to conclude it today and then
we can move on to the other areas.
It is.
Yeah, sure.
This is pretty much what we discussed on
Friday.
Nothing new.
I've just put everything in a sequence
like what Samant requested.
Can run you through it.
and take a confirmation on a few things.
Yep.
So,
I just wanted to start by confirming that
this will be focused more on I sag.
It's an Integration expert.
The screen is somehow not clear to me.
Others are able to see the screen
Was it?
properly.
No, same.
Ohh, OK, now, now it is better,
now it is better, yeah, yeah, good, yeah.
No, no, we can.
Abhishek.
Okay, sorry.
So I just wanted to start by stating that
our primary focus is going to be ISAC for
flow agent and...
Good.
This is what we had seen last time you
start with a prompt.
And agent will be able to tell you that
whether to use a flow service or a
workflow.
In case project is already available and
agent can is also able to find that
accounts are set up,
it will say that I will use this specific
project. User has to confirm that yes,
continue with this or pick from other
projects or create a new projects.
All of this have.
been defined in workflow so it's not part
of this deck.
At this point, user,
the agent can ask some questions which
can help,
no basis the prompt that the user has
shared.
User can either answer these or user can
say continue with your assumptions.
In both cases,
we should be able to generate a business
and technical view at the same time.
We had agreed that we'll have a vertical
layout for a business view.
This is just a directional,
I've just put the design.
This is not like finalized.
You need to still talk to Launchpad team.
But we all were, you know,
we wanted to have something more vertical
because the number of steps were much
higher.
Then workflow,
and also this is aligned more to a,
you know,
how a integration expert would use.
You can see the technical view,
which will be similar to what we have on
product.
And you can also then check the mapping
for each step.
And once you're happy,
you can create this flow service.
You have to explicitly mention create
flow service or click on this next action.
Okay.
and your flow service will be created.
Once that is done,
you can continue making changes or you
can test it.
Once you're done with testing,
you can decide where do you want to
deploy it.
Say, in this case, you continue to,
or you want to deploy it on cloud runtime,
do it and flow services deployed.
So yeah, this is the flow.
I've highlighted things that we discussed
last time.
So if there is any further discussion we
want to do, we can continue with that.
Any questions, happy to take.
Hey,
this technical view is shown only after
the flow is created, right?
Four.
Technical view is created along with
business view.
Because the idea is we have the project
account is set up and user as agent has
Yeah.
also asked a few questions to clarify.
So the business and technical view should
Huh.
Hmm.
be generated at the same time.
Play the song.
How is it with workflows?
Workflow earlier we had said we need to
share it before a project is created.
When the prompt is generated,
we want to show the technical view, sorry,
business view and technical view.
Then we said after project selection,
Little.
Mmh.
technical view is, you know, visible.
Current implementation is the you select
I don't know.
a project.
H.
You start with that business view
generated, we have to do some,
I just.
there is a button to validate
configurations. Once validation is done,
that is when we're generating technical
view. But there is, again,
And.
there was a discussion in that Launchpad
3 IB, Santosh, if you remember. So again.
What's new?
There was a pushback from design that it
has to be consistent to what we have
designed and Ramu Kumar,
he had said that he will review it.
So I just want to set a similar
expectation that once you have project,
you should be able to generate both
business and technical view.
Prasad would be can.
I don't think that may happen, Jyotish,
because for creating a technical view,
Okay.
you need some additional data,
like custom actions, custom triggers,
account selections.
I don't think that that is possible,
and why we are changing that behavior now?
I remember.
That is the behavior which we had set in
the design. It is not like, you know,
it was not followed in the integration,
the current launchpad that we see in
testing.
Expectation was that only, right?
And you've already given your project.
That means your accounts are already set
up.
So I've also assumed that your account
setup is done.
That's why you will be able to show the
technical view.
No, account is just one information.
Apart from that,
Mm.
we have triggers and custom actions.
So without those information,
the technical view is not possible.
So those things should have been
clarified upfront.
Is it not along with the project account
or is it a separate?
Separate flow again.
Is that a question for me or Thanmayi?
I know, in general,
I'm asking everyone that it's not for you.
So, so,
so before we go into that question,
one question to Jyotish, so...
Mhm.
The.
What is that implemented for workflow
today? Forgot about the Design proposal.
What is there for the workflow today?
Yeah.
Project selection.
Then we see a business view,
then there's validation,
We got.
there's a validate configuration or
something it's called.
You validate and then you see the
technical view.
Mhm.
So the validate step will capture
accounts.
What are all the information it is
collecting?
Ohh.
Project accounts.
So what exactly is happening inside
validate?
I'll have to check is Sonal on the call.
Can someone answer from the engineering
team?
So good joining.
I think this is the DSL validation that
we need to check.
No, no, I'm talking about the workflow.
Workload, okay.
Maybe you will clarify.
No workflow, project, account, trigger,
all these things happen in the beginning
only.
Good.
Yeah, I'll check with Sony.
Okay,
but the behavior should not be completely
Okay, Ashok is here, maybe.
different from what we have today.
And I don't know whether we can generate
the technical view without having a
conselection custom actions.
Trigger is not there for the flow,
so we don't need to worry.
But definitely the custom action is
mandatory.
For creating a custom action,
we need to have the account.
So, slow, yeah, sure, but child, I get.
Correct.
Okay, for having an account,
we need a project.
So, so far, work low.
So we need to make sure that these three
assets are already there before we even
Scenario.
Chicken.
show this technical view. Okay,
but someone from the engineering team can
answer whether we can show this technical
view without having all these things.
Really?
So on Friday when we discussed,
I think we also said that can this be
done in the back end?
Why do you need to tell the user to
validate and get it?
And I think there was some agreement that
yes, that can be done in the back end.
Like you don't really need to tell the
user that yes,
please validate and then we'll look for
No, no, no. Sorry to interrupt.
It's not like we can't do right.
these configurations.
We have to show user that what we are
trying to do, right?
Or whatever is intended,
we understood correctly or not.
That is what the intention of showing it
for approval.
So I think that the ultimate question is
can we show business view and technical
view together is the question.
Yes.
So I think now Friday also we discussed
and I kept it as a DVD.
I just looked at the wMio. Okay,
so we need to decide, yeah,
how we want to do it.
So business view and technical view,
can we generate at a time and then show
it? In fact, Ramu was also telling, okay,
if the persona is a bit of a developer
kind of a persona, technical person,
they prefer to see the technical view
first rather than business view.
Kind of a thing. OK,
so from that perspective.
Yeah,
both business view and technical view
better we generate together if it is
technically feasible.
That's my thought process. Just a minute.
On the use side,
if the flow Jason is there,
No.
we could render it out.
So today also the computation is based on
the flow Jason. So if the same flow Jason,
if the, if the, you know,
API is able to get that response,
then we'll be able to generate it out.
OK.
But if flow Jason generation is not
possible at this point in time,
then it will be able to.
You know, render the technical view.
Yeah,
without accounts we can't do it actually.
Yeah.
At least for custom actions and other
things.
Yeah, Namita.
So I'm saying that I think this we should
just sort of whatever is happening with
workflow right now,
the same pattern will be followed. Also,
this thing about the business view,
see the whole point of business view or
the value that it brings is that users
today when they're typing a prompt, right?
Like they first want to know if.
if the, you know,
if AI has understood it properly, right?
And that is why the business view can
break down that problem very nicely for a
user to sort of go through it step by
step and be able to make edits, right?
So I think that's the purpose of a
business view.
A technical view certainly is for,
you know, you just want to see sort of,
you know,
how further that is being understood by
the agent.
So just sort of clearly defining the
difference between the two.
Today, flows, you know,
only after the workflow creation,
Of.
the technical views generated in the new
launchpad. So, in workflow,
Is that what is is that?
how they how they have done this is how
they have done this,
Wu.
they have different modes,
they have a mode called draft and they
have mode called.
So initially you keep your workflow in
draft mode,
but behind the scenes the workflow is
actually created.
And once you activate it,
it moves from draft mode to active mode.
Okay.
So that's how they manage it, but without.
So, so we will,
so we'll use the same format here. I mean,
M.
we'll not make any changes here.
Do we see the need to make any change
Back there.
here?
Um...
That's what my ask as well.
So for workflow, we have preview.
And.
Okay.
During that time,
we show the business view.
You should.
There will be no technical view.
And then the workflow will be created
I am not asking for.
with all the necessary information with
the draft state. And then after I test,
That was.
then I'll activate it.
Then it will be moved to activate.
Okay.
Active state.
And why can't we follow the same process,
even for the flow services also? That's.
On my, I'm not, it's not the same key;
you do have same key,
So that's going to be the same time.
The idea is that if we already have the
see the response again.
project, we have the account,
why can't you create a custom action in
the back end and show the technical view
as well? Earlier.
No, no, no, one minute, one minute.
So you are making everything is simple,
And.
but let me ask one question.
Assume that you have 5 projects.
How will you decide which project I need
to pick and choose this flow service part
And.
to be created?
Some interaction to be there.
You will select a project, right?
That is the first step.
Thank you.
No.
I have not changed that. The first step,
see this,
No, where is that happening?
That's what I'm...
I'm first giving the option whether you
want to go with flow service or workflow,
right? Then project selection.
And I'm assuming that accounts are
already set up. That is why in this case,
I'm saying these projects are.
available for you.
Like you can please go ahead with this
project or you can pick other projects.
That means account is already there.
Yeah.
You have selected a project, right?
You can ask questions. Okay, I need this.
Okay.
Can you give me clarifications?
Then I'm creating a business and
technical group at this step.
So this is where a technical view is not
possible. That's what I'm saying.
So you have selected the account.
Mhm.
But where this custom action will be
created if this use case can only be
solved using the custom action.
Because some data to be added,
Mm.
the method to be selected,
and then you have to select some
attributes, the discovery,
all those things should be there for the
custom action.
So where that is happening?
that that should be no,
that should be done as part of a
questioning itself or immediately after
the questioning.
See here we are asking some questions
about it. Okay, so based on this,
the next step should be that one.
You see what other assets that are
required.
Paint.
Or something can be created behind the
scene. I don't know. Maybe, Ashok,
Hello.
you can answer that. You have project,
you have an account. Now,
the ultimate goal is to create a flow
service. And in between,
to create a flow service,
we also need to create a custom action
using these two metadata.
project and you have an account.
So is this something you can handle
internally before even you create this
technical view? Maybe you need to tell me.
No, no, we need to ask user only.
We only have object details,
No.
Big.
but we should ask user only to have other
details for it to create it.
Correct.
So for creating a custom action,
even today we are not asking this detail
Yeah.
to the in the workflow process.
Earlier in the world design,
we used to tell explicitly to the user,
okay,
this is the custom action we are going to
create. But with the launchpad design,
it's not explicitly asking.
OK, there is a custom action, right?
It is an implicit.
Maybe someone has to see that behavior
with the launchpad.
I have not seen workflow.
I'll just have a look and we'll come back.
Yeah, that's what I'm suggesting.
So have a look and have a word with Sonal
Mhm.
and then we need to arrive to a
conclusion how this can be aligned
exactly the same way because custom
action creation is nothing different for
workflow versus flow.
I'm seeing both are same,
nothing different.
Hi, I'm just, I'm sorry,
I'll just interrupt here, Prasad.
So, so whatever it is.
Yes, both are same.
Do you think for this, I mean,
even the last time I was in this call,
we were having a very similar discussion.
Should we look at what workflow exactly
is doing in some of these scenarios?
And if we feel there are anything that
you know that we need to do differently
for flow service.
then we take care of those things.
Do you think we can have a look at it?
Maybe tomorrow's call today,
it's already 3.50.
So just to sort of get a run through,
we can invite someone or somebody from
this team itself can kind of have a look
at what is being built for workflow.
Because then only a lot of these
questions I think will get resolved
because I believe quite a few of us here
have maybe not seen it up close and in a
Mm.
lot of details.
Yeah,
so you see there also I know in workflow
there is no specific questioning like
this, okay? But the steps,
whatever we are discussing, right?
For example, look up, okay?
So look up will happen at this stage,
okay?
And it requires a custom action that a
custom action happens at this stage
exactly.
The really I think.
No, but custom actions was a big,
big journey in workflow also, right, Tam?
Correct, correct. So what I'm saying,
this is where it starts.
Yeah.
This is where it starts.
Before even presenting the business view
and all,
the journey starts here for anything that
is required.
That's my understanding.
So here also,
it should happen here on means even for
the flow,
it should happen at this is the right
place because you see this fellow is
asking questions, right?
Some high level questions maybe.
Then it may have to go into some specific
questions saying, you see,
I need a lookup for this so and so
connect.
Okay, because there is a lookup field,
how you want to resolve it. And similarly,
So.
I want some custom action to be used.
Okay, if it is straightforward,
it can use,
otherwise it may have to ask some
question around the custom action.
So.
So Prasad,
as far as I remember in workflow,
the only prereq for business view,
technical view,
I'm still thinking what was finalized,
but the only prereq was the,
I don't even think project selection was
the prereq. Jyotish,
was that the case or project selection
was a prerequisite?
Yeah.
The project selection is a Pradeep.
Ill.
Earlier,
we had earlier we had when we had
Project selection was a...
discussed the design,
it was not a prerequisite,
but when we saw the test,
when we given the test tenant,
Mhm.
we realized project selection has become
a prerequisite. We had a discussion,
P.
and then we agreed that fine,
we'll need project for certain use cases,
so...
That is the first step in workflow right
now.
Okay,
and then beyond that the business flow
The.
will be generated, right?
Yes.
Okay.
So, our earlier workflow, wait, wait.
So, so, so now...
Yeah, one minute, Jyotish.
So my question is, okay,
based on this proposal, the same proposal,
the question is for the engineering team.
What is the challenge we have to meet
this ask?
If something can't be achieved,
maybe we can discuss. Otherwise,
we'll always come back and have the same
square.
So I hope you all understood the flow now.
Is there a challenge to achieve this?
Okay, silence means yes or no.
or you need time.
Achieve,
you are asking achieve what the current
experience user experience.
Yeah, so,
so to fit this current experience to
create a flow service,
are we envisioning any technical
Oh.
challenges? Say, for example, okay,
we need this object, we need that object,
so otherwise,
how we can fetch these things? So,
so if you could come back and tell, okay,
this may not be possible, then we can.
discuss. Otherwise, I mean,
it's like a repeated loop.
Okay.
Okay, I see Sonal joined. Okay,
so the question here, Sonal, is, see,
Of.
for flow,
even before going to the business view of
the flow agent,
do we need to ensure that all the assets
that are required are available or not?
For example, lookups, for example,
custom action.
So where that should happen.
It should be preconditioned like prior
generating the planner.
That's what even I am trying to explain.
Yeah, it is a precondition.
What is this?
Even in the workflow, it is like that,
right? Sonal,
Correct.
it's a precondition before even
generating a business flow. Okay,
so I'm telling this is where we need to
embed anything that is required. See,
this is a high level questioning what I
see.
Right. Similarly,
any assets that it requires missing
should be embedded here.
That loop custom action got to be created
or used. OK, if it is clear,
it can go ahead and use it.
If it is not clear,
it should seek a permission to create it
or something.
Lookups similar.
So here it should happen that okay,
I am trying to use some Slack channel.
What is the name of the Slack channel?
Is A lookup example. Okay.
Let's say it has to use some other public
service.
It has means all that is not there,
but to see if they come tomorrow, right?
It has to say that, okay,
I am already seeing a public service is
available for this purpose. Can I use it?
Okay, so all those questions,
you would come here only.
And then it goes into the business view.
That's my understanding from the workflow
as well.
Workflow is also behaving the same way.
Is that clear?
Amit Jyotish.
Yeah.
Are damn are you okay with it?
Yeah, so,
so what my recommendation here is,
since Sonal was heavily involved on the
workflow implementation,
someone from the flow side to have a call
with Sonal and run through this,
including Jyotish. OK.
And if Sonal identified that, okay,
something is different from workflow,
then they can negotiate how this can be
fit in order to solve this problem.
If something is not even possible with
the flow path today, whatever we have,
then we have to come back and tell, okay,
this may not be possible with this flow
proposal. And if needed,
we can change the flow.
That's not a big deal. Otherwise,
we can change the code to accommodate
this proposal.
So either one has to happen, right?
Okay.
I have.
So we need to take some concrete step
based on something.
The something is this design.
That's the base.
And the other something is workflow.
That is the base. The new thing is.
flow.
Now we need to see what is the difference,
how we can solve this problem using the
flow, the design proposal.
That's what I am curious to hear from the
engineering team,
spend time to understand the flow,
and then come back and tell the
Okay.
challenges. Otherwise,
we cannot optimize this flow.
Okay.
Even if it is 10 days.
OK, OK, clear, clear, dump.
I think one more point I want to.
Yeah,
I don't see any problem from flow service
Yeah.
if it is a DSL generated that with that
DSL flow can be generated the and the
account anything should be the
prerequisite upfront before generating
that planner and DSL that should be the
and should be there in hand. OK.
Ohh.
Yeah,
but one more thing I want to add is like
in workflow,
there is something called if something is
not there,
then we are proceeding ahead and we are
asking user to configure it in the canvas
like accounts, let's assume.
So to the accounts automation is not
there, okay.
So either option A is like create account
and proceed,
like create account that will get synced
to UAC and upfront in the chat that
synchronization will happen like okay now
I have configured my account and user
will come back. Second option.
should be given to the user is okay if a
user is not comfortable adding the
account right away.
So he can just proceed and create a flow
service or workflow.
So at least that artifacts is getting
generated inside the project and visually
user can also see the unconfigured part
of it. So I think that.
So this is where I created one epic for
workflow, right?
Got it, got it.
User is able to create a workflow even if
there is an error.
Correct, so that is happening today,
but in flow service,
Right.
Okay.
we need to see because there was a design
change overall,
like before account selection,
we would not be able to proceed with
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, this is where Sonal,
you need to spend some time with the flow
lookup and all, right, so.
team and how we can align towards the
overall experience, the AI experience,
because they all have very good knowledge
on the flow services, right?
And you have good knowledge on the AI
experience per se.
then you both have to sync and get this
sorted out.
Yeah.
Okay,
so we'll catch up tomorrow and if Sonal
That's block time, yeah.
and the flow team can spend time to come
back and tell what is possible and what
is not possible with the design proposal,
then we will revisit that tomorrow.
Yeah, yeah, I I agree. I agree with that.
Prasad, can you drive that?
Yeah.
I agree with that. So, Sonal,
I am giving these questions,
three questions. I am giving on your name,
but tomorrow, Ramu is also there.
Before the meeting, right,
we can discuss and conclude and come up
with our observations. Okay.
Are our input?
Yes, but Prasad, before that,
do we have a happy path with us so that
at least we can start the UI part of it
and then we can parallelly look on the
Correct, correct.
edge cases or corner cases?
Exactly, so that is what it is.
What Jyotish is sharing right now is the
happy path.
Jyotish, is it complete?
I see that still there are some missing
It is.
pieces.
So can you confirm if you are still
working on it or?
What?
Which are the missing pieces?
The execution history, the test report,
right? It won't be same as the workflow.
Yeah, I need, yeah, I need that reference.
So someone can help me with that.
Okay.
And our flow service can accept an input.
How do we provide an input?
My as in multi-term conversation.
We can configure input and output.
So, Alim,
shall I suggest you maybe spend time
After mapping.
Ohh.
along with Jyotish and see if whatever is
the gap, maybe you can update him.
Yeah,
that's why I wanted to understand if this
And then, yeah.
That the flow signature.
is in progress or is it complete from
your perspective?
Yeah,
this is exactly I also want to have a
conversation with the Sonal because this
is exactly the data mapping in workflow.
Right.
Yeah.
A limit that flow signature should be
part of the DSL.
This is.
Workflow we are not supporting.
The whatever LLM will generate that
should be part of that,
the flow signature.
Okay.
We are not supporting mapping changes,
right? And on workflow right now, it just,
Okay.
M.
From from.
it just showing whatever is generated
right now. We can't,
I think conversation mapping,
I think that's another epic.
Jyotish we have.
Yeah, so Biswa.
Yeah, so Biswa,
if signature is defined by the LLM of the
system,
then the user should be able to provide
the values right while running the while
testing the flow service.
So how do we?
Right, after deployment.
No, in this step, so Jyotish,
can you just proceed,
go to that slide where you had the test
flow service?
Here.
Yeah, just before this.
But it is just preview, right?
Technical is the preview, right?
No, no, on the right side,
if you see there is a suggested action
says test flow service.
It's just like it assumes that there is
no input for this flow.
But what if we have a signature for this
flow?
Support you.
To understand.
something draft deployment,
you can test it, right?
Thank you.
Dave.
The DSL will have that signature.
No, no, one second.
Hey, do we allow to test the workflows?
But then.
But only when it's active.
Do interesting.
It is only while it is active.
Probably the Iyer, after working,
that we can deal with.
After workflow creation, we allow that.
But.
But even then, right, see,
generally what happens is usually in flow
Hello, this is.
services you will have document types as
input,
where there will be a number of fields to
pass as input data to test the flow
At.
service. So,
where do we pass on that data?
To be.
You can just.
No, one more in technical.
See, the user, if it is a SLM test,
that to be payload can be generated based
Yeah.
on the DSL, right?
To.
This is.
That's an assumption, right?
I'm asking the flow.
No, no,
I'm asking check and see I what on frame
what we have done as part of the flow
pilot.
Pardon me.
Thanks.
Go to.
The current DSLs are getting generated
with the input and output structure.
Okay that.
And after deployment,
also pre-deployment can be done with that
I know.
Yeah.
signature.
And we either K.
You, you,
you create a mock data with that, is it?
Correct.
Can you?
LLM can generate OK.
Oh.
Yes,
but if I as a user want to customize it
Yes.
out, how do I do it?
Customize means you want to change the
signature structure.
No, not signature value.
Hello, OK.
I want to, you know,
give my values and test whether it's
working or not. How do I do it?
See,
you can integrate that once the
deployment or the pre-development,
the existing UI, the component, it's,
The next one.
and there is a run dialogue, right?
That can be integrated, right?
Ohh, that.
Then, then it.
And then it has to go to the tooling,
right? It is not in this UI.
Hello!
That's why we're trying to ask.
The tooling that maybe, huh,
if the Jyotish can integrate that.
OK.
Is it?
Six.
No, not in the tooling, right?
Technical we should show what is the
payload of this, right? At least schema.
Okay.
Skin, not Jason, okay.
Uh, their input, output, payload schema,
it should show, right?
Yeah.
Thanks.
So, I didn't get a question.
Let's assume webhook calls;
if webhook is there, webhook payload,
you are showing right?
Right, Sonal, in the workflow side,
it is no different than that, right?
Ohh.
See, if you are testing with webhook data,
right? It's explicit data.
Thanks.
It is coming from the user endpoint, okay?
Like wherever the user has configured the
webhook. Now, if you have to test it,
it will run with a mock data.
We say test mock data.
I'm not sure in flow service.
But...
Do we set the mock data or we have
already in the connectors we do have the
mock data?
No, we can set mock data,
but it doesn't work always, right?
If we have a character in that list
account, some get account is there.
That account ID should be there in the
connector, right? It may not work.
Mhm.
And also.
Account ID? No, no,
if error objects are there,
like if the workflow or flow service is
not completely generated, okay,
we should not give the test option to the
user itself.
Users should first complete the workflow
and then only that test flow service
option should be given.
Correct, we are not discussing that.
Actually, what we are discussing is,
let's assume this is the workflow, right?
This is a flow service, right?
Wu.
It accepts some payload, right?
With this UI design,
Okay.
I'm not getting to know what payload is
accepting.
Right,
I should know right at least schema.
And then we have to ask a question. Yeah,
we have to ask the question.
Question is...
A question is fine. In this UI also,
we should show that schema, right?
That to run.
In UI, we don't need, if you, okay,
so basically you're saying that the input
pipeline, we have to submit some data,
start date, end date, right? So let's,
Yeah.
Correct, correct.
I mean,
if that is a prerequisite for workflow to
Flow, flow, there is no trigger, right?
So it needs some input payload.
test.
Yeah, that is a static payload, right,
Ashok?
Yes.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
If it's a static payload,
then we have to ask user the input, okay,
in chat, in conversational way.
And we have to store that value as well.
And Jyotish,
you remember in workflow today we are
only showing mapping data.
Not the static data.
Yeah.
Similarly,
we need to show somewhere static data as
The API component.
well.
Whenever user update that static data,
like in this case start date, end date.
So where we will be going to provide the
read-only value.
Yeah,
I think that conversation we are anyway
having for workflow, but...
Will the designs be like similar in both,
considering the this mapping designs are
No, no, I don't think so. Technical,
if you are showing,
only very different?
if you are reusing the component,
I think Alim can give us the better
Mm.
insight. Are we,
can we reuse the component, Alim,
entirely pipeline input output?
Oh, yeah, even I had that question.
Are we planning to show the whole editor
in the treat mode?
because it is heavy, right,
with so many options.
Mm.
So if you are planning to show that,
then it becomes,
we do have it as a reusable component,
but here it might be unnecessary to load
or have everything, every option.
Thank you.
So this area in the artifact, Jyotish,
are you planning to have the same design?
Are we thinking of some other design to
represent flow?
I was thinking of using whatever is
already there.
The product.
OK, alright.
See, Alim,
recently I have requested already that in
Good.
that fix. OK, fix 12.1,
so I have requested to provide a service
This month.
Okay, it's okay, it's only in this okay,
which is insane, but it's okay.
with that without loading the node,
they'll give the signatures in the DSL
format. OK.
So that can be used by the LLM to part in
the input payload.
Okay.
Yeah.
But here we are missing that right in UI,
how will I pass the value as a user?
And how can I see what is the signature
or the input output accepted by the flow?
Yeah.
See, in one demo, I can share that. OK,
one minute.
No, I'm saying from the back end,
a technical point of view that might be
possible,
but here through the conversation,
I think the...
it should be surfaced to the user.
I think we can, I mean,
we can ask Jyotish to provide the
suggestion because ultimately for
workflow also,
we had the form based approach, okay,
where we were giving the input output
form data to the user to update and then
to save, okay.
But then there was a strong point that it
should always be conversation.
So, Jyotish,
like if you see the complexity of the
object, okay, it is very simple,
start date and end date.
But if there is a complex object like
structure where you have an object inside
Mm.
then there is an array and then we have a
string, then how we would be.
Hello.
No.
I mean,
that kind of complexity our system should
Thanks, Sanjib.
Something.
handle by taking an input.
Thank you.
Let's do one thing, let's block time.
I've put a few topics.
So one topic I want to talk about is test
flow. One is this mapping.
And I will just, I'll block time, Sunil,
with you and Aleemullah.
And I think others can also highlight if
there are certain things that you feel is
missing, please add a note.
We can connect and we can do a deep dive.
Yeah, yeah, that's what I would suggest,
yeah.
I think we can start with one scenario,
Prasad, the Ashok, Biswa, like everyone,
like exact prompt,
like this is the prompt,
like saying Salesforce account to HubSpot
contact by contact by ACV. So in this,
Ashok, the input would be.
What like it is always a map data, right?
There is no map input data for this prone.
What do you want to Singh?
What do you want to sync contacts data?
Yeah, contacts.
All contacts are in this particular
contact.
If it is all contexts that operation
doesn't accept anything, then we are good.
If it is some particular contact with
some ID,
then that should come part of payload.
Okay,
so identify the static data right away.
Yes.
So we can create one flow service
manually,
give it to Jyotish and there he can see.
More cases, like...
Yeah, we can do that, yeah.
Yeah, I only one question from my side.
See, where do we show DSL?
We are talking about this technical view,
right? It's a graphical thing,
but do we show DSL, sorry, FSL,
FSL any place?
The.
No.
Do you want to show that?
You can show that what this is the
graphical representation of the vessel,
Will be up.
It's.
right?
Correct, correct, yeah,
but do you want to show FSL directly as a
it's kind of a code, right? Yeah.
Yeah,
then that is so we can have one more tab
There is no plan.
or one more source link or something can
click and see that.
Yeah,
because we are giving a lot of focus to
FSL. So that has to be shown somewhere.
That's my strong feeling.
But,
but why should customer know about the
facet, right?
No, no, that, that,
that's the that's going to be the,
what do you say,
the center point for means there is focus
on FSL, that's what I understand.
That is a corporate way of doing it right.
Here we have better UI and everything.
Why should we ask customer to read the
code instead of seeing UI?
No, you've required, because see,
that's what that's what it is, right?
My understanding is that FSL is, see,
FSL is this is the core, okay,
from which this graphical interface is
generated and from which that.
That's the.
XML is generated. So going forward,
FSL will take the center stage.
That's my understanding from at least
from Flow Pilot and other areas also,
Yeah, there are.
right? So the question is,
user might want to see the FSL because it
I hit.
is easy to read than the graphical thing,
right?
OK, that depends on person.
But if you want to park it, that is okay.
If you want to park it, that's fine,
Gupta.
but that's a question I have. See if...
Prasad, there are two things in workflow.
So we have this DSL, okay,
Do you?
intermittent language from where we are
converting a workflow.
But do we really require to show over
here like it could, I mean,
if that is the case,
then while generating a workflow or flow
service in the canvas.
Then also we should be able to make a
preview of that FSL or intermittent
No.
language,
whatever we are writing using NLM. So.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
we we can't compare this with the
workflow, workflow,
whatever that that's I don't think that
No, no, it's the same.
It's one language is there which they are
is.
following and it is getting converted to
flow object. Okay,
but the second point I see is if we are
doing that,
then we have to store the equivalent FSL
in our DV or somewhere in the file system
where...
This is getting stored right, Ashok.
Okay, let it be an open question.
That's fine.
Yeah, shouldn't be a feature, Prasad.
It should be, I assume,
Yeah.
SLM.
it should be product feature, right?
In our product view also,
Yeah, it should not be.
Oh.
we should be able to see,
then automatically it comes here also,
Yeah, yeah, correctly.
Correct.
That's what my point is.
It's a product feature only.
right?
We shouldn't be debating that currently,
Thanks.
yeah.
That's interesting.
You want to leverage that one here, OK?
I had asked Tom about it.
I remember he said that we should like,
Ohh.
let's not do it right away. We can.
Okay, fine. That's fine.
I think, Jyotish,
all these answers which we are getting
But, yeah.
right, we should compile it somewhere.
Otherwise, I mean,
this is something Prasad, I also heard,
like how user can see the FSL,
Okay.
read the FSL, which is getting.
So maybe for the technical user,
Yeah, yeah, it's documented.
makes sense.
Okay.
See, when I asked him,
he said it's not needed right now.
It will be probably it'll go on the
product, but not needed for the agent.
Yeah, yeah.
But maybe we can ask it in our next call.
You never know his response might be
different,
but that's what I'd heard from him.
But I also agree with Sohan.
Let's document, I think.
That's fine, that that's fine, so...
We have a lot of discussions.
Let's document it.
Maybe it'll be easier to just.
Yes, yes, yeah, I'm sending a MOM. OK,
this point is also covered in that, so,
close things and move on.
so if you want, you continue this meeting,
I'll connect separately,
so let's say by tomorrow let's have some
more clarity on especially the gaps and...
any technical challenges that we have.
And you want to see the generate,
you want to generate business or
technical views together from a UI point
of view, Aleemullah,
maybe you can see if there are any
obvious missing pieces we can discuss.
So if we have this by tomorrow, right,
that would be great.
And one more thing, Jyotish,
the business view which we are generating,
K.
right? It's a plain text.
It's not a view currently. So, I mean,
Mhm.
should we eliminate the business view?
I mean, just a thought process.
Do we really need to bring that business
view?
We can,
we could have shown that in the right
side of the chat panel itself,
instead of creating an artifact of it.
Like in the right,
where we are conversing.
on the chat,
but I also heard that business view might
end up becoming very long in some cases.
So it's ideal that we keep it in a
workspace versus on the chat. And again,
if we remove business view completely,
it'll be a deviation from what we have on
workflow.
So I think we should also have that.
Consistency.
Okay, but it is not a view right today.
It's just a set of steps.
I mean,
it's not a graphical view right now.
I didn't get that.
Let's connect on that separately then,
Sonal.
Okay, sure.
I'll block time with you.
Are you and Aleemullah,
are you guys available like today in the
evening in block time?
We can continue over this call itself if.
Yeah.
Seven.
At least we, we get, you know,
continue with,
but Aleemullah have how comfortable you
are in exporting this entire widget into
this technical view.
Right now it is a separate component,
UI component,
but we do have a tight coupling with a
React application,
what we have in Integration UI.
So we have to still see. But still,
if we have to do that complete thing,
it's still questionable. We have to see.
And also.
And.
Because it is a read-only beep, right?
Maybe we can have a lighter should.
Yes,
and I think certain input items have to
be removed.
Right, there are a lot of like options.
Got it, got it, yeah.
Yes.
Like you said,
it has to be more simplified.
The idea is to like, like,
remove a repetitive work and create a
Yes.
It.
different design.
That's why I think it's good to have some
to view something which looks very
similar to what's on the product.
And in flow,
do we generate an error object or
something like this state of the flow?
Because I know that we can't save the
flow itself.
Correct, we can't see when I rest it.
Correct, we can say, you know, that is,
that's the validation you put on the
tooling, but Jain, as in flow,
there is no such rule that you can say
with low errors as well.
I think only,
but for the some of the it can be a
So who is looking into it, Ashok?
subscription,
so things in been monitoring.
Ashok.
Santosh, Santosh.
What is Santosh?
I have not looked at your day slowly.
So much.
The.
This.
Tell me.
OK, what in looking into means which part?
Could you please elaborate?
for generation of flow.
Who's looking at the generation of flow?
I thought you guys were already working
Yes, that, that will be your,
but what are the capabilities in there?
on a POZ on that, Ramu and you guys.
Ramana,
generation of floor generation of DSL.
No, that we are looking into.
OK.
Those things you do, yeah,
pass all the instance like.
Generation of flow, this UI, you know,
works on the flow Jason.
Yeah.
See,
two complete things: the DSL is the Rama,
Yeah.
what is that they're developing the L.L.M.
part that they will generate the DSL.
And from DSL did we generate a Jason?
DSL to flow is the ISN build
functionality.
Thank you.
Ah, okay.
No, no, it's not all that is all instance.
Yeah.
No, but the Biswa,
can we get the flow without with errors,
like the...
Without with error without IS also we can
convert the DSL to flow without runtime
Nobody's followed.
But is that the subscription loads?
also in per preview in the UIC in
Aleemullah and Santosh you need a JSON
okay right the flow JSON can be
transformed from DSL to.
People, OK.
Great, that's great.
Big Bhusan.
That Jason without us also, OK?
You need to write some piece of code that
Yes.
Yes, yes.
will that can be generated, OK?
Without us, even in designer also in,
Yeah.
I can run flow without us,
I can generate a flow without us.
You guys think?
OK, that can be done. OK, so.
Thanks.
The transformation from DSL to flow can
be done. OK.
Yes, yes, yes.
I think Jyotish has pinged that UI screen.
Alim,
you need to check if there are some
missing pieces in that XML or how we are,
The.
If you have to support the API level
integration for those things, then yes.
how we can indicate.
Ohh, the original next week.
The visual thing experience,
we have it already. Okay,
Thank you.
if there is an error in the step,
we can display that error.
And Biswa is confirming that a flow can
be saved even with the error, right,
Red, red, red, red.
Biswa, with the DSL.
DSL should be valid. DSL with error,
DSL cannot save. OK,
That.
Yeah.
means saved means in IS,
you need to call that API, right?
Convert to DSL to flow the conversion
only possible if it is a grammatically
correct, not like I'm.
Using a wrong invoked service service is
not that that is OK,
but some syntactical or grammatical error
that conversion will fail, OK?
If the target service is not there,
that's okay.
That will get flow will get generated.
That design time is like I am expecting
Those are runtime errors, not design time.
invoke, but you are putting invoke one,
invoke two, that is.
No, no, Design time.
What we had validate is with those drop
down that you see, right?
Are they not blank?
Do you do you have if if there's a
connector,
Uh-huh.
do you have an account configured?
Do you have an operation configured?
That will be there,
maybe that account anyway that is the
prerequisite right account configurations
without that the DSL that and this is the
Yeah.
prerequisite right? The project name,
connection name,
This is only those are the validation
that we do in the UI client layer.
this are the prerequisite right?
SNL and the mention in the first
beginning of that.
Before that planner, the DSL,
this account,
or whatever the required account details,
everything should be the pre-configured,
I mean prerequisite.
So only after that technical we will be
generated.
So, only through that, technically,
we will be generating.
Right, that technical view of business,
and see,
as I know that also can confirm that what
Rama is doing that LLM,
it generate both DSL and planner and the
same time, right, Ashok?
Currently we are not,
but we can make it happen. Yeah.
See.
Okay, then what is this process?
First business, then technique,
DSL or what?
Currently it is like that,
for it levers business and then technical.
That is what currently it is.
Then,
then why we have to then all together,
But...
then that?
No, no, no, no, no, Biswa.
If you see the designs,
first business will get generated,
and once user says validate the plan,
then business technical will go hand by
hand, right, Jyotish?
Then this some UI change is required then
this UI is need to be changed because
I want to eliminate that.
he's showing both business and tech
parallelly.
Yeah, I'm showing both. Yeah,
I'm showing both. So Sonal,
this discussion came up also in that
Launchpad 3 IB that why do we need a
validate step?
So I just want that.
Okay, if we are bypassing the validation,
then we can go ahead with that as well.
Like business and technical,
like why was that the point raised that
we should do validation just like since
user has just prompt a given a single
line prompt, right?
And we wanted to give first business view
just to cross-check whether that.
Business prompt is well taken by AI or
not in.
Chat.
In that case,
we need change in this view then.
So we had that discussion.
I'm assuming that we'll have that
alignment on that call as well,
and we'll generate business view and
technical view at the same time without
the need of a validation.
So I would just want to move in that same
direction so that we don't end up having
two different experiences.
The earlier discussions, Sunil,
if you remember the very earlier
discussion was when you write a prompt,
generate a business view first,
then ask for project,
and then show technical view.
That was the expectation. Then it changed.
We said, no, first we last project,
Yeah, yeah, no, no, I am like...
then we'll generate business view and
technical view. And now we in the when.
When we saw the thing,
we realized we have also added a
Yes, yes.
validation step,
which is not in the design.
So it is still getting contested right
now.
Okay.
So I have one question for flow or people
like if the business view is getting
generated, okay,
let's assume your system is unable to
create a custom action at that moment.
So in the in the technical view will we.
We will be able to show the.
A custom action without an operation
because operation is not yet created.
So operation name would not be there.
Only the application name would be there.
So.
Can this happen at Flow?
Yeah, Sonal,
it will be shown as a empty or error,
Thank you.
as if the account or action is not
selected.
Only connector has been selected.
Okay, so from the DSL,
the FSL point of view, Biswa and Ashok,
if you don't have the operation.
FSL checks only syntax. OK,
if syntax is there, it will generate.
That's what this also.
No, but if operation is not there,
an account is not there,
you won't be able to get fetch the
signatures also.
So it would be just connector data,
like connector application name.
That's it.
Correct,
it is like invoke service with wrong
service name it assumes and no input
output. That is what FSL assumes.
Correct.
Okay,
then we can generate the technical view
over here as well.
But the experience would be like too much
RT, right? You chose an error,
a lot of errors,
and then the user will have to ask user,
and this won't get updated dynamically.
The technical view.
No,
but it every prompt it will get updated,
right? Let's assume in the second call.
No, no, I am saying if I keep it open,
the user can't expect that it gets
That is still happening for Wu also.
updated. So you have to close, open.
So the experience is a bit more chatty,
right? You have to ask so many things.
And this we will still stay with error,
Barry, got it.
which is not desirable.
Like what we have right now for workflow,
that seems to be fine.
You have a business view,
which is more of a plan.
And then you ask a couple of questions
and go ahead and implement.
Play.
The implementation is the technical view.
That is more seamless than showing up of
workflow or the flow with error and so
many other incomplete steps.
And then you go ahead and ask so many
questions and get it updated.
Can I get an example of this?
Let's build it, I think.
IT.
Let's build one.
We can't build, we can't save it,
actually. Ashok, can you do that?
Ashok dropped. Alim,
will you be able to show that one example,
like without operation, how it looks like?
Yeah, sure.
But the point is, Jyotish,
what I also feel is at every conversation
Yeah.
that technical view is getting updated.
Why? Because in the business view,
we were not fully sure that what to
create and what not to create.
Mmh.
And every conversation that new technical
view is getting generated. So.
What happens is that data is not getting
dynamically updated. Okay,
it is on every chat you get an artifact
data. User needs to open that.
And then?
M.
So every time it's a number of clicks has
been increased now, like I chat,
There is another discussion happening,
Aleemullah is aware,
I get some.
where you want a technical view to get
refreshed. I think that for workflow,
Aleemullah should remember the
conversation with Keesa and we said post
Yeah.
Yes.
Know that.
GA will,
so that will get addressed if we are able
So that we need to.
to.
auto refresh it.
I know there are too many moving pieces.
I'm just...
Yeah,
I think same thing will happen for flow
also.
So maybe we can write some of the points
which are common for workflow and flow,
like the mapper enhancement which we are
doing, the re-rendering of technical view.
Again, these things are very, you know,
So, so let me understand one thing.
heavy.
Okay.
So, Sonal, right now, also,
if you on the work on workflow, right,
It.
I can like build creation,
I can create a like technical view with
the there will be some errors when I say
create this workflow.
When I click on create this workflow is
when I last last starting start asking
questions, okay,
which slack channel do you want?
Where do you want to do this?
Right.
Right, and then once you are ready,
you will be able to test it.
Correct. This is happy.
This is happy path. But what if user says,
Right, and it will get created like once.
Happy Bapat and what?
I don't want to submit the input,
just create it. Okay.
Then also it should be visible into your
product and with unconfigured state error
Mm.
states.
Okay.
So, what, what is the problem then?
No problem. Like we can't force user to,
you know,
fill all the data and then we would be
able to generate it into the actual
product. So in flow also,
we have to give the similar behavior.
Like either way you give a happy path
where user is giving all the inputs,
whichever, whatever it is required.
Else,
user can say skip all the validation and
proceed creation of workflow.
Then...
Workflow doesn't support that. I mean,
I I told like the agent to like go ahead
do some make some assumptions and all
creation didn't happen,
it just stopped me there.
I think there is some alpha, but yeah,
we are aligned.
Are we allowing?
Create the workflow is the prompt,
I think,
which enables you to call the create and
save code.
Mmh.
So using the question that that get asked
after you click on create workflow,
if you don't answer,
it should still be able to create a.
Workflow,
which will be visible on product with
with errors.
Correct.
But then we'll still need to enter those
fields right before you test it.
Yeah, that is, that is,
that was users come change now in
requirement, right?
Users not ready to fill over the chat,
and I mean, since we are creating it,
user can go and do the ProofIndiaContrIBM
product and update and test it,
so this is.
how we are not enforcing user to submit
everything via chat.
But in the current workflow,
which is like on test right now,
is it possible? Can users say, no,
I don't want to fill it?
Mhm.
Yes, it is possible.
K.
It is possible.
You want to see that?
You can, yeah, we can.
Jyotish,
I was just wanted to show how the how it
Take a look.
will look if the user doesn't configure a
custom action on there.
This is how the steps would look.
You.
The policy.
And then, yeah.
Hello?
And put.
Sorry, can you come again, Aleemullah?
Yeah, yeah,
so we are discussing about how it would
Did.
look when there are empty actions right
if we have to show technical view before
Ohh.
accepting some custom action or getting
the answers from the users right before
Okay.
configuring the step.
This is how we'll see a bunch of error
It's.
steps and then the user has to provide
all the information.
Do you see?
So that is what I feel,
not a desirable experience.
Just a minute, please.
Whereas if I open, yeah,
this is what I tried earlier.
Bygone.
OK, here.
And, tell me something.
We have this business view. Okay,
somebody. I click on it.
I don't have a technical view because for
this to be enabled,
But you, that's just what you have to do.
I need a couple of information.
Like here it is asking, right,
Yeah, open it, manage it, yeah,
what is there, like, what is there, like,
which account to use and custom action,
all those things. Once this is available,
it will generate a technical view.
And when I go to technical view,
I'll get the complete.
workflow, how it works, right?
Whereas imagine if I have to show
what is there?
technical view here itself,
then it will be like bunch of errors or
nodes which are not clear,
things like that, right?
Part knowledge agreement.
You understood what I mean compared to
this and complete flow.
Dave.
I, I,
I can see a very different experience
Baby.
though, Aleemullah.
Can I share my screen for like one minute
on what is just my own get more clarity?
Sure, sure, yes.
See over here, my screen is visible,
right?
Yeah.
So I've selected the project, okay,
and it has created this.
Only business views possible. I said,
okay, validate connector operations.
It says everything has been configured.
There's nothing pending at this stage.
Now I can see the technical view.
So this is happy path.
You have everything configured.
What if nothing is done?
So can you give me examples of what are
the missing configurations?
Yeah, I just showed right the account.
There are multiple accounts or the which
one to pick the same for the custom
action.
So here everything is working.
Here only these details are missing.
Slack channel and couple of other things
which we are showing after we create
No,
I think trigger is still not configured.
select create workflow.
Look up.
Trigger is still not configured, and...
It could be the case.
That slack,
there are multiple accounts for slack
application.
So maybe during chat it will ask right
slack one or two.
Yeah, that's what it's asking. OK,
it didn't ask me about slack one or two,
Yeah, well, while...
but without that we can't proceed on the
workflow agent.
Correct.
It won't generate the technical view.
That is what I was showing you earlier.
I had that slack one account selection,
which one to be selected?
That question is not appearing here.
Can we ask those questions then?
That's the reason why, like on the design,
I've given the option to ask some
questions.
Can we ask these questions or like,
or in some cases there'll be too many
We are asking you right, Jyotish.
things?
We are asking, yeah, see here.
M.
This is what was talking about.
Yeah.
Slack has multiple accounts available,
so which one to select one of them?
So this will happen when I click on
validate. I'm saying,
can we ask this without even clicking on
validate?
Can we ask these questions upfront? Like,
why do you need that extra button?
I'm not saying don't ask the questions.
No, I think validate. So what happens,
Jyotish? Business view,
let's assume you are asking for something
and your product doesn't have that. Okay.
So what is happening over here?
The technical,
the business view is getting generated
irrespective of what we have or what we
offer or not.
Like if you say do or create task in
Slack, okay,
and there is no operation like create
task.
in the product. So the question would be,
should we generate the business view just
Mhm.
to, you know,
logically represent the prompt
translation,
like the prompt to business logic
Mhm.
translation,
or should we do not generate the business
view for that and explicitly say, okay,
we do not have a create task.
Did it rated him, Thanmayi?
Go in Slack, so...
Look at all.
Call Gupta.
Do you want to?
And the most of the songs are the other.
still continue or want to select any
other option, something like that.
Mm.
So the understanding was to generate a
business view,
irrespective of checking whether that
operation exists or not,
or whether that accounts are available or
not for that particular.
Mm.
Application.
So Jyotish, in simple words,
the business use more like a plan,
Mm.
like to do plan.
Like this is the prompt is translated to
Mm.
a business intent or how it should be,
like more of a to do plan.
And then it goes into that implementation
phase,
which is more like a technical way where
we need a lot of information like
accounts, custom action.
Like if this is send message here,
but what if it is something else?
All those things are decided after this
validate step.
So that's where I was asking. I mean,
I thought this is the right way of doing
Mm.
things by at least user should find it
graphically that okay,
something is not present in the ProPoint
product. Let's assume over here workflow.
Then how should I navigate from here?
Like should I in future it could be like
should I create a connector?
And then proceed,
or should I go and start creating a
flowser with the same plan?
I mean,
some kind of unification should be there.
M.
No, I get your point.
You basically just want,
before showing a technical view,
you want some details. Happy path,
there won't be anything.
So in the happy path,
can we just proceed and show the
technical view along with business view?
Okay,
wherever there are things that you need
to ask, we can figure that out.
Sonal Ali.
Example.
But.
Sorry?
Just tell us that, what was that?
I'm saying that in a happy case where you
don't really need anything from the user,
What?
can we then generate the business and
technical view together?
And wherever we need more details,
we can ask those questions and then
generate the technical view.
So you are saying bring both the things
on the plate,
like generate the business view and
technical view.
No, one second.
Then what is the purpose of that?
Deleting both at once, right?
But how you will generate a technical
view?
If you are doing both at once,
what is the purpose of it is serving?
It's almost similar,
only if some initially.
It can keep only one, right?
The allowed, sorry, need need of what?
I didn't get that, Ashok.
When we generating both at once, right,
what is the purpose it is serving?
You eliminate one step now for like
certain use cases,
you don't have to again say validate this.
So go ahead and generate it if you have
everything. If you don't have it,
you can ask the user, yes,
I need some more details before I can
generate a technical view.
That is fine. If there's no way around it,
like let's ask them those questions.
No, but over here it's not the user,
it's like product is not supporting that
operation, okay, entirely.
Like if you say I want to generate ABC
operation, okay, ABC is nothing.
In our product, it's an unknown entity.
What user will do,
Mmh.
but at least giving business view prior
to this will help user to understand that.
Web message Vorap is.
OK, we thought ABC is the operation. OK,
from the picture it would be much clearer
M.
that, OK,
the system understood ABC as operation,
but I was saying.
ABC as an input.
Like there could be some way of the tone
Yes, fix it.
of prompt was different and LLM
understood it as an operation.
Correct. What I was thinking,
the purpose of doing business wave is my
Separate.
understanding and whatever user gave is
correct or not,
Eng.
is matching together or not.
It is not because something is missing
you want to ask, right?
That is what I assumed.
The system, you, you,
I need to define something.
Correct me if.
Correct, even I agree with that, Ashok.
For me, it is more like a plan,
like what I intend to do without the
system understood what I intend to do.
Correct.
Give us for another.
Yeah.
I might have understood everything,
something very wrongly,
Which, which we utilize for then creation,
deletion,
even though all the services are there,
but we should get a confirmation.
failure in that is the instance creation,
then same we are right now testing in
I thought that was the...
Intention, if that was not the intention,
then we can go with different discussion.
lower environment, but probably.
Yeah, Jyotish.
subscription will be.
So, Jyotish, you can come back on this,
like either somewhere we have to show
Mm.
So, the thing is,
tenant creation deletion,
like depiction that this for you,
this user Brown,
we thought this is the connector,
this is the operation. Okay,
did not have any alerts implemented. Hmm,
because there was also now implemented
and then we can proceed ahead from that.
Also, I mean,
the better way is to give the business
view or...
for tenant creation.
In the chat somewhere we have to show the
set of steps also, right?
And similarity, something, so that, that,
that,
This is what we understood with this
single line of statement.
What's what user is giving to us.
that understanding is the business view,
right?
Yes,
so that understanding is a business view,
like breaking your prompt into set of
steps so that we can cross validate, okay,
Jordan.
this is what is required and should we
proceed ahead. Now once we proceed,
Work with Mehta.
then only we validate whether this
operation is possible or not or not.
Then you did sort of find out.
How do I learn?
whether this connector support this
operation or not in our system.
How it will, like, how it will be,
what will be done or?
So happy path would be, it will always,
it will support what user has given and
So, for that,
you came up with a vector in hand,
we'll go ahead.
But what if that operation is not
supported? So we'll come back and say,
okay,
you can completely differentiate this is
called production, this is for you know.
we don't support this operation currently.
And here is the next step.
Like either you can create the,
you can ask or request the administrator
You speak English.
to add the operation for the connector or
you can.
Ohh, one thing you said, but provision,
provision, we check now, so the broad A.W.
Create your custom action or REST API.
There could be multiple steps to it.
guys, broad as you, yeah.
Yeah, I see, I agree with you, Sonal,
on that, but what,
that's what I was trying to say,
that you can ask some questions if you
want about the prompt.
You can even ask them, okay,
this is what did you mean this user can
input or user can say, no,
I don't want to reply right now.
You can just go ahead with assumptions.
This is that can you generate a like
business and technical view.
When I select and create this flow
service.
Can you then ask me,
because can that be the validation that
okay, before I create it,
I will ask you these other questions.
Instead of doing 2 level of validation,
right now we are using create as a
validation,
we are using that validate the workflow
as a validation. There are two steps.
Can we bring it down to one?
Why do you need two different levels of
validation?
No,
but the technical technical view is
purely in the product, right?
So you can't generate something which is
not there in the product technically. OK,
that is.
Even though, even though it's a draft, it,
it'll still get,
it'll still get generated on the product.
No, no, no, I just understood this.
I understand this point. Like,
let's assume for Slack,
user is saying ABC operation. OK.
Do you want to give higher visibility to
production,
I can represent it in business view. Why?
Because this is a business logic which we
or do you want to give the same
visibility as production,
are deriving from the user statement.
But today I can't generate a technical
and then people should pick up or lower
environment also,
view. Why?
Because ABC operation is not there in the
but they should check the lower
environment.
system.
I think there is.
Okay, in the system, in the sense,
it's not there in the product.
Will you have fun?
We are not supporting this kind of
operation for the slack.
Have you seen JENA?
Who should come up with this?
So, for this, OK, for this.
Who should come up with 10? OK,
I will not.
Since I can generate the business view,
should I continue showing the business
view or should I restrict over there
itself and converse back to the user
No, says OK,
I want it to be easily identified in
saying that, okay,
I can't generate this technical, I mean,
Mumbai, and I said, whatever.
I can't generate this flow service
because we don't support this operation
It's weird.
currently. So how we should represent.
Is good.
Back to the user.
So that is why we were never blocking
technical view.
Got it, got it, got it.
Only business view,
we would be we were showing it first,
Got it.
I mean, as a first view.
So is there a possibility that we
generate the business view and ask these
questions along with it saying, okay,
I have generated the business view.
Please answer these questions and I can
then show you the technical view.
Can we do that?
But that's what we are doing right today.
We are doing validation. We are saying,
okay, validate this workflow.
And then we are asking.
these questions.
I'm saying show these questions along
with the business view.
Maybe for a lack of better terms,
we might have used validate,
but that is what is actually happening.
We are asking a couple of questions and
then we are getting those updated.
Not the final validation as such,
not the test.
Yeah, I get that early,
but it's still a step is what I'm trying
to convey. It's still a blocker, right?
I can proceed.
If I have certain things,
why do I have to say validate and then
show those questions?
Because in most cases,
when I say validate, it says, okay,
everything is configured,
everything is fine, proceed.
In some cases, it'll stop me and say,
okay, no, these things are missing.
Yeah.
So, what is alternative in that case?
Instead of validate,
how can we frame that text?
So I'm saying instead of asking the user
to take another action,
can we just put those questions?
These are some missing things.
Once you've answered this,
I'll generate a technical view for you.
Let the user answer.
Let's not add a step and then show
questions.
Let's show the questions up front.
Is it possible is what I'm asking?
I'm not giving you a solution right now
on the call.
Okay, Jyotish, you are saying that okay,
do the validate step as well.
Like trigger it manually and if you are
blocked,
then show why we are blocked and else you
will proceed creating a technical visit.
Yeah.
So that validation that validate step
should run in the backend.
Automatically,
it should not block me if I am,
if I am because business we understand
the logic that yes,
we will show whatever is written.
We are not even confirming it,
but I'm saying for technical view,
if the prompt is correct and we can
generate, let's generate. If not,
let's block the user, say, you know,
to generate the technical view,
I need these answers.
Like,
type these answers to these questions to
see your technical view.
Okay, I think fair enough.
I think we need to check the
implementation then. Ashok,
we would be able to do it right.
It's A precondition step for us.
Yeah,
we should be knowing already what all
things needed for that converting that
business view to take help you.
Mm.
But it will take time, Balaji,
like validate what we thought just to,
you know, give the experience, okay,
confusion.
Sonal, your audio is not clear,
it's breaking.
I.
OK,
what she is saying is it will take some
time back and lot many back and forth
things would be happening. OK,
for creating the technical view business
view is just LLM understanding with the
Mm.
Yeah.
data. That's it.
It is simple to show business view,
but that that time taken for generating
technical view is much more.
Mm.
Than generating business view.
Gotcha, okay,
so you're saying to generate the business
view also the time taken will increase
now. Right now,
business views are getting generated say
instantly.
Yes.
31st year.
If that is OK,
means we can go ahead with the product
plan.
What will be the difference? Like 2x or...
The.
A small percentage.
It depends on the prompt and the
connectors.
I.
Yeah, if it is bigger prompt,
it can be more than two X also,
Mm.
because there are two-month flow calls
will be happening between product as well
Mm.
Iyer.
Gupta.
as and the yeah, LLM.
M.
OK, those API calls go on the delay.
Actually,
if there is some network or some slowness,
it may be more than double, yeah.
Got it.
Let me do one thing.
Let me think about it.
Let me put that in design,
whatever I was even proposing.
Let's see if that makes sense and maybe
we'll catch up once Tam is also around.
But in the meantime,
can you give me like for this?
prompt that we are using.
Can you tell me what kind of questions
will be needed before generating a
technical view?
But I can put the right examples instead
of saying, like, select account one, two,
like, if we have...
Specific example.
Have I shared the prompt on Singh?
Yeah, before going through that example,
Sunil Tam mentioned in Launchpad
M.
experience for creating custom actions,
workflow is not asking any questions.
It is automatically deciding and creating.
Is it true?
Correct, correct.
In custom action,
there are so many custom headers and
parameters people can add that we are not
giving option for user to do it.
No,
we are using the default payload which a
connector has set and proceeding ahead.
But usually people will add few many
things right in custom action.
That can be, yeah,
so once that custom action is created,
right, the workload is created,
maybe edit of custom action,
like how we are giving edit support to
custom action, right,
then there we user can do the updates,
but at the first shot, agent take,
like we had a discussion over this.
So time proposal was to, you know,
do not ask too many questions or like
this is the configuration set of steps,
right? And as a business user,
I won't be much comfortable doing that.
So it should take the defaults and should
proceed and should.
proceed with creation of custom action
and creating the workflow.
Then we can select accounts also,
whatever is comfortable for the agent.
Just proceed, don't ask anything, right?
No,
if it has only the single account
configured for that,
it will take out the code.
If there is no account,
then chat will say, okay,
add it and then come back to this
conversation. Or if there are multiple,
then it lists like, okay,
we see account A, account B,
account C is there.
Which phone do you want to select and
close it?
OK, there also, we can select one.
OK, please,
since this is user credentials,
you want to be much careful, right?
Is that the reason behind that?
Pradeep.
Yes, I mean, if there are multiple,
actually,
if we see we are order selecting that
account if there is only one account,
okay.
They were not given the option.
To the user.
Yeah, and then account is the only thing,
right? Other than that, nothing we ask,
even with custom action also.
I think lookup we are asking,
like once the custom action is created,
like behind the scene,
and if there is a lookup data required
for that custom action to be configured,
then we are asking that lookup
information, the user int.
For look up also,
we are discussing on on feature where
look up also default value should be
provided if, if, if it is there.
If that comes, then...
No, not static lookup, dynamic lookup,
like lookup based on the account.
Okay, okay, okay.
Look up an accounts we're asking.
Those are the two additional things will
Yes, but if user is not configuring it,
okay,
come in.
let's assume the lookup calls get failed.
It will proceed with creation of a
workflow today. So what happens,
like sometimes accounts get deactivated,
right?
The accounts which are there in the
registry.
So, look up call is getting failed. OK,
we have seen this example and since I
mean, since it's a conversation,
so what we are doing is we are continuing
creation of accounts and then we are
asking user that to change. I mean,
just check the errors that we are not
able to configure the lookup at that
moment of time.
So, this is 1 edge case, Jyotish,
where we where an MPI to fetch the data
is failing.
Mmh.
And we go with that error state that,
okay,
we are not able to add the lookup for the
given operation.
And because that count got expired. Okay.
So today, we so in the experience itself,
we are not asking the accounts again.
Instead,
what we are doing with this expired
account itself,
we are creating a workflow.
Okay.
Well, I think.
That change in, you know,
I mean the communication which we are
doing,
like why we are not able to proceed with
this account,
like just because whatever the reason we
are not giving enough data upfront to the
user in the conversation that due to this,
that is getting failed.
You remember last time when we were
having this discussion with Keesa,
the error state one?
Yeah.
API phase with 401.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like for different scenario,
there's a different probability,
but we need that also in flow. I mean,
it should be common in both workflow and
flow.
Yeah,
I think those things will be quite common
between both. See, I mean,
you have to define it for now.
I think we've we...
He thought of something right on that
call itself.
I think it's documented.
We were actually discussing about the
artifact only,
but in during conversation also we are
doing multiple validation call or
fetching data call.
So if those calls get failed during
Mm.
conversation,
like I'm asking for a Slack channel ID,
okay?
And the account which I have in the
system is called.
expired. It was valid few minutes ago,
but it got expired somewhere.
Hmm.
So I am not able to retrieve the channel
information now. Okay.
So agent,
what agent gets is 401 unauthorized.
So what agent will say, okay,
looks like you're not authorized to
retrieve the data.
Mm.
Now what will happen?
User needs to configure the account again.
M.
Yeah.
So how, I mean, how, in how,
like in better way,
how we can ask user that, okay,
your account seems to be invalid and you
need to reconfigure it. So,
so basically user is going to step one
again, configuring the account thing.
Yeah.
Mm.
Okay, I'm just taking a note.
I think let's list on all these scenarios.
That's like as a separate bucket as like,
you know,
error scenarios can address that.
I will also try to create one list by
tomorrow. Okay.
These all are our edge cases, although,
but yeah,
Yeah.
I mean we have to solve this problem.
For both flow and workflow.
But Ashok, coming to your point,
custom action should be should get
Got it.
created with default parameters and look
up, wherever look up is required,
we need to ask user input.
before creating a flow service.
Okay, okay.
I thought a custom action would say more
extensive journey. Okay, I got it.
What you are doing?
Okay, if the same experience needed,
then only two things we may need.
One is if delayed mappings.
Means lookups, other one is account,
that's it. Nothing else for clouds.
And Ashok,
who is looking into the Dev account sync
process?
Sridevi.
Okay,
do I mean is this schema shared to her
like how the accounts needs to be stored
in USA?
No, those can be directly piece.
It doesn't need to be.
Right.
Go.
No, I think it should be in USA, right?
No,
it it will finally it will get synced to
Okay, I was.
USC because workflow also supports staff
accounts in the future.
It will get synced anyway. Got it.
Let her prepare first API,
Yes, yes.
then we can go to USC team to get sync it.
OK,
at least I'm expecting at least an API
from her.
Once she gives,
we'll ask UC team to sync it.
It is needed for both workflow flow in
future at least.
Yeah, we have to think of that here,
or Jyotish, or like...
Ashok, the experience would be same,
right, as close,
M.
because there are some more.
No, there are some more,
but we are going to default right then.
There's no difference.
We don't want to go with additional
things, right?
Okay.
But in some of the cases, right,
in future,
if you are supporting the rest and soap,
right,
We are looking for the.
there are entirely many things we should
ask for creating custom operations, like,
like soap and all,
we are asking and all to upload for soap
But I was in Viktoria Museum, actually.
custom actions.
If those are custom connectors,
system X operations.
But, I will say.
But I think we are not covering those
cases for now, right?
Mm.
Or should we include that as part of
Design now itself?
No, I think Ashok,
we have we need to divide the scope.
I'm not sure.
Tan said that custom actions are also
there in the scope.
Mm.
A custom actions are there, right?
There are two different kind of custom
actions.
One is like standard closed stream custom
actions, right?
Yeah, for standard only,
we in workload is standard till now.
Standard means it is same.
There is no difference. Actually,
there are characters also same.
Template to dynamic loop.
So, if you...
No dynamic,
but there is a format in which it comes
the same,
like there will be default lookups and
other things,
since she told it lookup is available for
flow. Also, it is similar experience,
but if you come to technology connectors
and other places, it.
Becomes different.
Okay, Jyotish, I'm sharing my screen.
Okay.
OK, I tried creating a workflow. OK,
so over here the account present for the
trigger node was expired.
Mm.
Okay,
so it created a business view and
technical view for me where this is the
view.
Yeah, we will start with the, but uh,
you asked about the blocker, right?
Like, it's on configure taken.
That's what the GAP is, uh,
for the getting the what is that they
No account was since account was expired
during creation.
already configured, and the...
I said start work with creation.
What is, you know,
what we are going to post it that one,
It created a workflow, OK?
not so we will not separately.
This really.
So.
One second.
And also, edit, edit, editing.
Just not like it.
Posting, posting.
So it created a trigger for me,
but since it was the account was expired,
Okay, okay, okay. I'm getting, getting it.
Yeah, it will be same. Yes,
maybe put on the, yeah, yeah.
I was not able to save from here as well,
because then I got to know the session
expired or invalid. So today,
while conversing, if I start this process,
Mhm.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. First time also,
it will be update on that.
OK, and something is...
Some API call is getting failed and
although I'm skipping it and I'm creating
Yeah, yeah, got it to share.
a workflow. So somewhere in the summary,
a summary kind of thing,
Mhm.
we should give that.
I mean,
notification proper notification text box
Yeah, I will start up from U, yeah.
that I attempted creating a trigger,
but it got failed and or I attempted
creating a custom action.
I got few errors and we can display it.
So, during the process,
if something is getting failed,
Mm.
then how we should showcase back to the
user that this is.
Fix the we are giving today we are giving
very generic statement.
Fix the missing details.
Mm.
I didn't fix the phone. Got it.
Exactly what is missing is not getting
captured.
Alright.
So today,
if we can say if I have fixed it and
proceed.
Go ahead.
Then it should work from there.
I'm not sure what will happen.
This.
No, it's not fixed.
Income,
I really need to help with testing or
activating.
Since.
I think this kind of edge cases are still
there. I mean,
we not sure what the experience over here.
Because agent calling tool and because
user is confirming that I have fixed,
Yeah.
but let's assume in the background does
not yet fixed.
Yeah,
let's look at the edge cases once you've
like finalized the happy part.
Or.
The test part.
But, for heartbeat part,
do we see any gaps, Ali?
That test part I think was left.
What do I show in this test report?
I've just shown whatever is there in
workflow, but is it the same?
This workflow be.
Like when you open it,
what will I see over here?
on the workspace.
I think it's there and flow.
Can you share a screenshot that I can
just use? Or what do I generate it?
As Alim told,
Flow has so many things actually.
I'm not sure how we want to.
Maybe Alim and you can discuss what
exactly you wanted to show.
It has multiple options actually.
For test, test report.
No, not only test.
There are many other options other than
test also. But how much you want to show,
you can decide.
I think Tam was very clear that we just
want to go ahead with something.
I think that I'm assuming is already
defined.
I'm sharing my screen again on Jyotish.
Yeah, that's what I told you to decide,
yeah.
The.
So once it is tested, no,
we need to show something like this.
It is successful. This is the report.
This is the report.
That is actually response, Jason,
actually, that Jason or some XML,
whatever it is.
That is a response coming from the test
operation.
And.
Since it doesn't have any input, but...
No, no, it works. Just turn it, it works.
No, no, I wanted to show that input thing.
Add int by edit.
Ohh.
We can click on add from input output
signature in the same panel.
Yeah, I over laptop set.
We can depend on IO. No, no, not here.
Not this. Cancel.
Just in the same panel you have this
right add from input output signature.
Yeah, here. No, no.
Input field.
Click on Reset.
Can reset.
OK, so.
Wait, click on the plus here, here,
just give done a given a name,
List.
Give something.
So, dynamic, right?
click on done.
No, it's that.
But.
Just give some name.
No user can give any name to it, right?
The key,
Yeah, yeah, any name, any name.
but can't we generate this using AI or
something?
Yes.
Yeah, this will be generated. Biswa said,
yeah, user will not define it manually.
Ah, that we can do.
We can just queue for now.
This will be automated.
But we ought to show it at least.
Yes.
Correct, we have to show.
Ohh, this, but this document type.
And leave it, then.
Click on Done.
Document type and all.
Yeah, if you run, don't map. Aha, anyways,
you can map.
You just wanted to see that run input,
right, run dialogue.
Control, now you will see that value.
Still, it will fail her.
Still, it fails, then think it is.
Okay, I think this is Jyotish.
Do something.
This is like at the time of execution.
If something is there in the input
pipeline, then user will type and proceed.
So in conversational way,
how we can do it.
Does this need to be solved now?
Yes,
I think for many of the cases the input
is coming from.
We need to configure some start tag input
to test the workflow.
So this will happen before you test.
This will happen after creation or before
As he did.
creation.
No, it will create like this only. Okay,
let's assume it created a property called
M.
data. Okay, which is user input.
And while I'm testing it,
Mm.
I know that I need to collect this data.
Mm.
Okay, so when user says, okay,
I want to test the workflow of flow
service, I say test action,
then the tool will call to collect this
data from the user. Okay,
so this data is having string property or
Mm.
any other could be the property.
How we should...
Say that, OK, enter the date required.
In string type, so in conversational way,
we have to, you know, uh, take that data.
So that can be solved, right?
We can just say, okay,
that this is the data, this is an example,
type it like this.
Yeah, this is simple way of doing things,
right?
And what?
But let's assume if there is multiple
complex data.
Can you show me some examples, Sonal,
then,
In the back.
because I'm not able to understand the
complexity?
Okay, go to IO. Go to IO, please.
Are you want me to share?
I think low is a bit.
Oh.
Which project do you have some project
where?
We'll create one.
Abhishek, you can check Abhishek project.
Abhishek, Abhishek, Abhishek.
I'll be private.
A BHKFSER.
I C.
A BHK under score IC.
Yeah, here you can just check anything.
Yeah.
FTP, SFTP, you can check RSMTP services.
But the description is not mandatory over
here.
Not Bennett.
It's optional.
Mm.
So, if...
But AI will generate appropriate key
value pair, right?
And it has to generate the description.
Director show.
Yeah, yeah, that's implementation, right?
Yeah, we can do that, yeah.
Yeah.
But I think it would be same as
conversational then.
If we are set of multiple inputs,
then obviously from conversational only
we would be able to achieve it.
No,
it can be a Jason also if you put it as a
record, right?
That is okay. Today in our workflow also,
I'll show you.
Yeah.
There are some connectors like ServiceNow.
I'll show you this one.
Pick up.
Singh is a legal problem.
I see that this is not the case.
It is not the case, it is the case.
Yeah.
Hey, we will check that.
Yeah.
So, let's take this example, OK?
Ohh.
Somewhere I have seen this.
Okay,
so this is a doc type and then it's a
value.
So today how it would be given to user is
I want a doc type reference. Okay,
so user will add that and then we have to
see at what layer it is like.
parameters, request headers.
So we have to put a placeholder that we
are asking this.
And then once we get the user input,
we have to observe that inside the same
object placement.
So this was one of the challenge,
like going from form based to
conversational, right?
So this we have to think.
The agent would be keeping that
placeholder.
And that placeholder needs to be asked,
and once it is filled,
we have to update that placeholder to the
actual value.
Yeah, okay, got it.
But that Jason looks much more complex in
real scenario and with much more feeds.
I agree, I agree. I mean, everything,
but I mean,
Jyotish also knows that how hard it was
for us to, you know. I mean,
Ohh.
we were against this conversation, why?
Because when there is a complex field,
when there is a dependent look up,
then it will, it will.
It would be a headache for a user only to,
you know,
Yes.
get the data submission done properly.
Yeah.
So, Sonal.
But.
We maybe had some alignment.
If we absolutely need to show a form or
build a UI to use a dropdown something,
if we can build a case, we can look at it,
but we agreed that let's not do it for
the first launch. Let's go ahead with it.
Also, there will be doing some tests.
We can continue,
Very good.
like we can invite people.
We can ask them to use it,
like capture what their thoughts are.
Mm.
And if you build a case, I mean,
we can definitely do it.
I don't think it's like a strict rule
that we'll not do it, but for GA,
we wanted to avoid it.
Just go with everything purely
conversational.
So if we have a specific use case,
we can definitely.
revisit that.
Yeah, I think we can that. Yeah, Jyotish,
I will suggest Ashok,
We have to build just build a strong,
we have to build a strong case.
someone is there from QA can give her the
better understanding of complex cases and
blow service.
Yes,
tomorrow I'll share you something complex
Again, create a project and can.
if you want.
I already have many things actually I'll
share you. Yes. Okay,
we already created by QS.
Yeah,
but our straight item focus should be the
set of which.
Sam has given at least a happy path for
that prompt should be enabled. So Jyotish,
like for this,
let's assume a simple field data is there.
Then are we going with that
conversational way or can we bring form
right away?
So this would be the point.
I get.
For example, just sharing my screen,
I can see this mapping. Say, for example,
this mapping, right, start date,
this is some mapping which is already
done, right?
There's nothing that is needed from the
user. Samant was also asking, like,
if I want to change the mapping.
No.
You know, can how do we do it?
I think he just wanted to have that
conversation.
I don't think he's brought it up. Like,
can we do it on this workspace itself
instead of doing that conversationally?
I think that was something that he was
mentioning.
No, it's a it's a viewer, Jyotish.
It will only be able to view the mappix.
Someone is a read-only mode, right?
It can only view the mappix.
Yes.
You can't do anything out of here.
Right now, right now it is. He was also,
he said he'll speak with you all that in
And then.
future.
Can we allow them to change the mapping
how you can do it on the editor?
But.
in this workspace later on, not right now,
not for this first build,
But.
No.
but maybe later on. So he,
I don't think he's then had the chance,
Okay.
but that's what he was saying.
OK, so Sonal, I still need this example,
like, you know,
if I click on detail run report,
like how we have something for...
Your workflow.
Like say we have something like this,
what do I show for flow service?
Can you share a screenshot that I can use?
Yeah, I will share, okay, some response.
Okay, okay, okay.
Yeah,
I think Ashok and Ali can share this,
Yeah, I will check, yeah, I will check.
but Ali may need to analyze it, like how,
I mean, are we going to rebuild or reuse?
Because we are also thinking Jyotish to
reuse the existing component. But yeah,
M.
like you remember when we were having a
discussion with Keesa,
Mm.
Keesa has proposed something for the
default values.
For test, for test.
Ohh, but what if...
Forward, sorry.
Not for test, for mapping data,
the pipeline data for flow could be a bit
Mhm.
complex, okay?
Plus the static value which user is
Mm.
giving as an input. Correct?
Mm.
That we have anyway is not closed, right?
That I think is an open point.
She just shared some things because we
were just having that conversation.
But let's look at both of them,
maybe together, so...
Let me block time with you and Keesa
Sonal this week.
Let's take that up because I not picked
it.
So, we need to highlight with this book.
I not picked it because it was not that
ticket is not prioritized. So I...
Highlight this.
Santhosh,
have we created that ticket for Design
Team to?
I don't think there's an epic for it,
but that's what I requested that we need
to prioritize that in three in a box.
Because there are a lot of other epics
that will get created,
things that we said will will work later,
so...
How you are tracking it, Jyotish? Like,
is it a user story or is it a defect?
It was a defect,
but I think there has to be a user story.
Something has to be created.
I don't see that now.
So I'll have to ask them because we were
supposed to look at all the issues that
we've said that, okay,
we will not do it now,
we'll do it later and then prioritize
amongst that.
We then we have a list of things that we
said we'll pick in H3, so Q3,
that list which was shared by Thanmayi
earlier, if you remember,
on one of the three, because so we, I, I,
I need to get the list and then ask them
that what is needs to be prioritized for
now,
like I know flow agent is prioritized,
that's why I'm...
Putting all effort on this and testing.
But what I see in flow also,
you are reusing the entire widget, right?
See, on click of a pipeline,
the mapping is appearing. So similarly,
Yes.
for workflow, can't we think of that?
I mean,
same reusing the same component while we
double click and.
We'll have to think because I was not
involved in,
I don't know what was the thought process
with what, with which, you know,
the entire mapping was built.
And if you remember all the conversation
Yeah.
we had,
we've had very little discussion on flow
service, on the mapping.
We've mostly spoken about technical
business view.
and projects, right?
So mapping I don't think has been even
Yes.
explored to that much. I mean,
from what I've understood.
So we might have to visit.
Yeah, that is true. I mean,
from piece of experience,
we only thought like only AI generated
mapping needs to be shown to the user.
Okay. But if we are saying that, okay,
configure the mapping,
at least users should be aware of what
fields are there, right?
Other fields which are, you know,
required to be mapped.
Like,
I can't simply say ABC under score T
should we map with this or something or
high level like priority should be mapped,
Mm.
but there's no key like priority in my
data set, correct?
Yeah.
So somewhere I feel if we can reuse the
entire widget, like as you have.
Gone for flow, but I'm still not sure,
Aleemullah, how much that is possible.
Also,
like to import the flow widget with
read-only tags.
Technically,
we have to see what is feasible and also
Jyotish like the mapper part for both
workflow and flow, how we can.
Bring the same experience like if we are
showing all the field metadata for flow
and workflow also we should give the same
view.
Who, who, like,
will that be added on the launch pad
workspace, or will it be like,
who's who's gonna prioritize that?
Will it be Tam or Gabe Pradeep?
Is there a lot of common topics getting
discussed? I just want to know.
Who with who picks it up,
who I need to speak with for
prioritization.
I think we can have this discussion in
three in the box,
Thank you.
C.
but before going for flow.
At least we should know for workflow,
and then we can compare and, you know,
sort this out for flow also.
M.
Go.
I think Santhosh,
you wanted to add something, I think.
Income.
I love you.
A center.
Sonal, can you repeat?
So what we are discussing is mapping in
other configuration, right?
Ohh.
Sorry.
The static info, the accounts,
should we show this in under artifact or
So, if he wants to...
only AI generated mapping should we,
we will be showing. Because if,
I was saying.
let's assume if the pipeline data is huge,
like input and output, then how?
Technically,
it is feasible to display under the
Something.
artifact data.
So it will be read-only right at that one
at that moment.
So, it would be that one that pop in.
I think Santosh, your voice.
No, no, no, I, I, I,
what is the what is the uh drawback of
having so much of data and that effects?
Okay.
Because we do have a lot, you know,
a huge number of data coming for projects
He's not proper.
Yeah.
and listings, right?
The flow Jason itself is a is a is a
heavyweight object.
Okay.
Yes.
Thank you.
I think we can analyze it once,
Alim for flow,
at least the pipeline thing, and Jyotish,
it looks very simple,
I don't know.
like once you click on that mapping
configuration, right? And that does.
Thank you.
So,
so see the the flow Jason on the very
Mm.
first intended,
it will not have all those information.
I do.
So,
what we do is when only when you click on
Hello.
it,
we try to fetch that our information over
an API call.
That's how it is done in the editor.
I just.
I need it.
Yeah, but if we need it in artifact,
we need all that information upfront,
Hey, what is that?
right? Maybe we can, we can optimize it.
It's not a big thing, right?
And even in artifact later,
only if we need click on it, yeah,
we have the reference of that, yeah.
And I can make,
we need not need all this data,
This is.
but flow Jason generally has this
information if there are forests.
So,
so any flow that we are trying to query
right, it it usually stores everything,
flow JSON itself,
Bye.
it has that information already,
it it usually flow JSONs would be all
like, you know, 3000 lines of code.
Thank you.
So, the...
Thank you.
The.
Cortana.
B.
I, I forgot.
I think we can continue the discussion,
Jyotish. Let us first check all the cases.
We can have it on, I cannot, I guess.
Hmm.
And will compile one.
All right.
Page for this.
Sure.
And we can have one discussion around.
Any specific reason why this was
recreated and not like it didn't use the
existing designs from the.
Workflow editor.
So...
So what is happening in workflow?
It is there is a canvas and when we
double click on it, there is an open.
Yeah. So it was overriding the behavior.
It opens up, yes, yes.
So experience wise, it won't look good.
Because.
M.
It is like, but again,
I mean there are some construct like loop
you have seen, right?
So we can go inside that loop and we can
check how many actions are there.
Again.
Mm.
So I feel this was designed because of
that thought process,
like multiple windows should not be there,
pop-ups should not appear. So.
Instead of giving a pop-up, it, I mean,
the rendering is like that.
There we are giving this tree view and
non-tree views.
And.
So earlier only that default view was
there,
The.
but then the point came that how user
will get to know that how many field
metadata is there for this to be mapped.
M.
That is why that tree view concept came.
But then there is a issue like if that is
getting mapped and if statics are given
by the user or defaulted,
I mean default selection has been done by
the system,
then how we should represent it.
So we are going back to that concept like
double click on the action and get the
appropriate view.
I have to go.
M.
OK.
Like we can have a discussion for
workflow,
Who will?
because in flow what I'm seeing is it's a
vertical displaying of things, right?
Like.
When you click on that pipeline icon,
it is coming underneath the.
Yeah, whatever is there in the product.
Yeah, not, yeah,
Editor.
we're not creating anything new.
Unless, like, there are challenges,
I think, Aleemullah, if you feel that.
I will have to make small changes because
this is very, I mean,
we can't show it exactly like this, right?
The canvas is like full page canvas and
now we are trying to bring everything in
this size. I mean,
we'll have to see like certain elements
if you see I've removed. I've hidden this.
There's like those overflow menu, yeah,
Yes, that's what I was indicating.
account, this,
all of this maybe we'll have to hide.
Then mapping also I've removed things.
I've hidden these.
This entire thing.
I don't think all of this will be
applicable since it's read only. I mean,
I will have to get into details. I mean,
I'm just.
Done a quick job just to...
Put things together.
So if, yeah,
I just think everyone should take a look
at this.
They can get into more detailed
discussion.
I think we are at a very high level right
now and we good that we are having some
detailed discussion,
but I think there's a lot that we need to.
Ohh, look at.
And we can think of these three points,
Jyotish, like for test input is required.
There's one more thought process that can
it be dynamically mock input can be
generated by AI because it is only for
test, right? Ashok Alim,
M.
this could be one of the things.
And second is report.
Report for workflow is different from
I think.
what is there in flow.
So you can have a look into it.
Thank you.
Wait, wait.
Anyway, it is all.
Reused component for both.
Yeah, Ashok has shared an example for.
Yes, and 3rd is like account selection.
Let's assume if there is already selected
Test report.
account.
and how we should default,
I mean how we should indicate that into
the artifact data.
I mean, this will be applicable for.
Now that flow XML comes with account
actually that is already will be there.
If it is selected in the flow example.
But it is a read-only value, right?
Correct, correctly, yes.
Yeah.
I'll get it.
Okay,
so same icon would be displayed right
Ashok the tick mark.
Yes, yes, that is the same, yeah.
The account is there.
And the green means it is selected.
Red means now account is there.
That's what we can.
But if user wants to see what account is
selected.
That user experience you need to think.
If you don't want to open Bapat,
we have to add some experience.
Are you really,
is it really needed to show?
Account for in a test report.
Now, in a view mode, technical view mode,
should we show account?
Okay, which account is selected? Workflow,
we're not doing it, right?
No, Jyotish, that is the open point,
right?
Sonal.
All the statics we are not trying in
workload with them.
Static, we'll find a way.
We'll find a way. Yeah,
So, the deaths are coming.
let's we'll find a way. The question is,
do we do we want to like,
like make one similar design?
Considering that mapping looks very
different for workflow versus flow,
I think the solution could be different.
Unless someone brings a point saying that
looks different,
it needs to be consistent.
That's a similar different topic.
But I think we can bring it up in
tomorrow's conversation, not 3.
Yeah.
30 sync call.
Let's also hear from Sam.
Yes.
OK, I think it's, well, it was.
Okay, okay, let's see. I'll leave 535.
Can we wind up by getting what clarity we
got and what we need to discuss?
Can we put one minute and we'll wind up?
Sonal, you want to put some?
Samant on this.
Yeah, I'll create the meeting notes.
Did you?
Okay, okay.
Okay, thanks a lot.
All right, thank you. Thank you, everyone.
This is a very long call,
Thanks for the dish, bye.
but very fruitful, I think.
But the Jyotish PM should be involved,
right? Whatever we are discussing,
we are just discussing like this are the
these are the technicalities, but.
SPM should be confirming it.
Yeah,
I think we should have some of these
Yeah.
discussions with PM because otherwise we
might just end up talking about a lot of
things and then...
He might say this is not relevant right
now, right?
Yeah, that is why, yeah.
Me.
So we might just enter into and get into
a rabbit hole and keep discussing and he
might be like, no,
this is not really needed right now. So,
but good that we touched upon a lot of
these topics that we have to and we can.
Continue tomorrow once time is there.
If needed, we can move that,
make that a one-hour call instead of half
an hour, like at least a few of them.
To close out, at least.
Yeah,
only one major clarity was what is needed
Okay.
for custom action. Like that we got it.
just account and lookups if needed.
That's it.
That is what clarity we wanted.
And other things we can again discuss
with P.
So, only put a point,
maybe let them confirm tomorrow,
that based on that, we can proceed.
Yes, K.
Okay, thank you.
Okay, thanks, Keesa. Thanks, Hari. Thanks,
bye.
All right, thank you so much. Yeah,
bye-bye.
Yeah.